O.W. Riegel Papers WLU.Coll.0387
Washington and Lee University, James G. Leyburn Library Special Collections and Archives
- Dupont Awards, 1943-1982; Riegel, O. W. (Oscar Wetherhold); Du Pont, Jessie Ball; Cole, Fred Carrington; Gaines, Francis Pendleton; 7.5 Linear Feet (Box 1-18, Folder 1-530)
  - Judges, 1951-1966 (Box 9-10, Folder 244-320)
    - Y-Z, 1951-1966 (Folder 301)
    - Multiple/Unknown Authors/Recipients, 1951-1966 (Folder 302)
    - Federal Communications Commission, 1951-1966 (Folder 303)
    - Forms, 1951-1966 (Folder 304)
    - Instructions, 1951-1954 (Folder 305)
    - Instructions, 1955-1960 (Folder 306)
    - Instructions, 1963-1964 (Folder 307)
    - Instructions, 1964 (Folder 308)
    - Instructions, 1964-1965 (Folder 309)
    - Instructions Misc., 1951-1966 (Folder 310)
    - Instructions Misc., 1951-1966 (Folder 311)
    - Instructions Misc., 1951-1966 (Folder 312)
    - Lists, 1961-1965 (Folder 313)
    - Lists Misc., 1951-1966 (Folder 314)
    - Photos, 1951-1966 (Folder 315)
    - Scoring, 1951-1958 (Folder 316)
    - Scoring, 1959 (Folder 317)
    - Scoring, 1960-1961 (Folder 318)
    - Station Comments, 1951-1966 (Box 1)
    - Misc., 1949-1962 (Folder 319)
    - Misc., 1963-1964 (Folder 320)
  - Kennedy, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 321-324)
    Items in this sub-series consist of materials related to the coverage of the Kennedy Assassination. The Dupont Awards foundation found it apporpriate to commemorate numerous stations for their detailed coverage of the event.
    - Agronsky, 1964 (Folder 321)
    - Bro-Col, 1964 (Folder 322)
    - Salinger, 1964 (Folder 323)
    - Memos, 1964 (Folder 324)
  - Lettershops, 1954-1963 (Box 11, Folder 325-328)
    Items in this subseries consist of correspondence between Riegel and various lettershops regarding the production of a mass qualtity of letters to individuals regarding the awards. Some letters focused on the errors by the lettershop businesses such as errors in the use of names, punctuation, and grammar.
    - Dav-Nah, 1954-1963 (Folder 325)
    - Nelson, 1958-1960 (Folder 326)
    - Nelson, 1960-1961 (Folder 327)
    - Nelson, 1961-1963 (Folder 328)
  - Lists, 1961-1966 (Box 11, Folder 329-331)
    Items in this subseries consist of lists of individuals based on association. Some of the lists of note in this subseries include a list of CBS correspondents, Dupont Award winners, and the Dupont Award Foundation Mailing List.
    - Lists, 1961-1963 (Folder 329)
    - Lists, 1964-1965 (Folder 330)
    - Lists Misc., 1961-1965 (Folder 331)
  - National Association of Educational Broadcasters, 1963-1966 (Box 11, Folder 332-336)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Folder 332)
    - Info & Publications, 1953-1959 (Folder 333)
    - Info & Publications, 1959-1960 (Folder 334)
    - Info & Publications, 1961-1962 (Folder 335)
    - Info & Publications, 1964 (Folder 336)
  - National Association for Better Radio and Television, 1959-1965 (Box 11, Folder 337-342)
    Items in this sub-series consist of materials published or sent by the National Association for Better Radio and Television. This organization sought to encourage quality programing for families and children. some items of note include a booklet of television programs with ratings and reviews and newsletters mentioning the Dupont Awards.
    - Orme, 1959-1966 (Folder 337)
    - Publications, 1959-1964 (Folder 338)
    - Publications, 1964-1965 (Folder 339)
    - Publications, 1965 (Folder 340)
    - Publications, 1965 (Folder 341)
    - Publications Misc., 1959-1966 (Folder 342)
  - Other Awards, 1951-1966 (Box 11, Folder 343-346)
    - Other Awards, 1951-1954 (Folder 343)
    - Other Awards, 1954-1956 (Folder 344)
    - Other Awards, 1961-1964 (Folder 345)
    - Other Awards, 1964-1966 (Folder 346)
  - Problems, 1952-1965 (Box 12, Folder 347-362)
    Items in this subseries consist primarily of correspondence addressing various concerns individuals had with the awards. These problems ranged from the permission of including some materials in various nominee presentations to the eligibility of certain networks in the Dupont Awards.
    - Ada-Cod, 1951-1966 (Folder 347)
    - Cole, 1963-1964 (Folder 348)
    - Cole, 1964 (Folder 349)
    - Cole, 1964-1965 (Folder 350)
    - D-E, 1951-1966 (Folder 351)
    - G, 1951-1966 (Folder 352)
    - Haefele, 1963-1964 (Folder 353)
    - Haefele, 1964-1965 (Folder 354)
    - Haefele, 1965 (Folder 355)
    - Haeff-Hil, 1951-1966 (Folder 356)
    - Hyd-Lyo, 1951-1966 (Folder 357)
    - Mic-Rut, 1951-1966 (Folder 358)
    - San-Tai, 1951-1966 (Folder 359)
    - Tho-Tre, 1951-1966 (Folder 360)
    - War-Will, 1951-1966 (Folder 361)
    - Misc., 1951-1966 (Folder 362)
  - Program Revision, 1951-1966 (Box 12, Folder 363-385)
    Correspondence in this subseries focuses primarily on the manner in which the Awards were determined and given. There is extensive discussion between Haefele, Spackman, and Riegel about the Trustee's involvment in the selection of judges and giving awards. The Dupont foundation wanted to increase its influence on the awards process, while Riegel thought that the Awards should have more liberty to act on its own.
    - Akr-Bro, 1964-1966 (Folder 363)
    - Cole, 1965 (Folder 364)
    - Cole, 1965 (Folder 365)
    - Cole, 1965-1966 (Folder 366)
    - Goodman, 1964-1966 (Folder 367)
    - Haefele, 1963 (Folder 368)
    - Haefele, 1963 (Folder 369)
    - Haefele, 1963-1964 (Folder 370)
    - Haefele, 1964 (Folder 371)
    - Haefele, 1964 (Folder 372)
    - Haefele, 1965 (Folder 373)
    - Haefele, 1965-1966 (Folder 374)
    - Mic-Pic, 1964-1966 (Folder 375)
    - Spackman, 1964 (Folder 376)
    - Spackman, 1964 (Folder 377)
    - Spackman, 1964 (Folder 378)
    - Spackman, 1964 (Folder 379)
    - Spackman, 1964 (Folder 380)
    - Spackman, 1964-1965 (Folder 381)
    - Tai-Misc., 1964-1966 (Folder 382)
    - Memos, 1951-1965 (Folder 383)
    - Memos Misc., 1964-1966 (Folder 384)
    - Misc, 1957-1965 (Folder 385)
    - Misc, 1951 (Folder 385a)
  - Publications, 1943-1966 (Box 13, Folder 386-398)
    Items in this subseries consist of documents by the Dupont Awards Foundation that were issued or available to the public, including: the agreements between the Dupont Foundation and the Awards committee, annual programs and brochures, and descriptions of the awards.
    - Agreements, 1943-1950 (Folder 386)
    - Agreements, 1950-1951 (Folder 387)
    - Agreements, 1951-1952 (Folder 388)
    - Annual, 1943-1947 (Folder 389)
    - Annual, 1948-1950 (Folder 390)
    - Annual, 1951-1952 (Folder 391)
    - Annual, 1961-1963 (Folder 392)
    - Annual, 1964-1965 (Folder 393)
    - Annual, 1966 (Folder 394)
    - Annual Misc., 1943-1966 (Folder 395)
    - Award Descriptions, 1943-1966 (Folder 396)
    - Mailing, 1943-1966 (Folder 397)
    - Misc., 1943-1966 (Folder 398)
  - Publicity, 1943-1966 (Box 13-14, Folder 399-424)
    Items in this subseries consist of correspondence about spreading the awareness of the Dupont Awards.
    - All-Brown, 1951-1966 (Folder 399)
    - Bye-Gre, 1951-1966 (Folder 400)
    - Lan-Mue, 1951-1966 (Folder 401)
    - Pan-Ric, 1951-1966 (Folder 402)
    - Sel-Swa, 1951-1966 (Folder 403)
    - Tai-War, 1951-1966 (Folder 404)
    - Correspondence Misc., 1951-1966 (Folder 405)
    - Photos, 1951-1966 (Folder 406)
    - Press Releases, 1943-1951 (Folder 407)
    - Press Releases, 1951-1952 (Folder 408)
    - Press Releases, 1953-1954 (Folder 409)
    - Press Releases, 1955-1956 (Folder 410)
    - Press Releases, 1956-1958 (Folder 411)
    - Press Releases, 1959-1961 (Folder 412)
    - Press Releases, 1961-1962 (Folder 413)
    - Press Releases, 1962 (Folder 414)
    - Press Releases, 1964 (Folder 415)
    - Press Releases, 1965 (Folder 416)
    - Press Releases, 1965 (Folder 417)
    - Press Releases, 1966 (Folder 418)
    - Press Releases, 1966 (Folder 419)
    - Press Releases Misc., 1951-1966 (Folder 420)
    - Misc., 1951-1960 (Folder 421)
    - Misc., 1960-1961 (Folder 422)
    - Misc., 1962-1964 (Folder 423)
    - Misc., 1951-1966 (Folder 424)
  - Public Relations, 1963-1966 (Box 14-15, Folder 425-441)
    Items in this subseries relate to efforts by the Dupont Awards Foundation to capitalize on their public relations. A large part of correspondence is with the Public Relations office of Earle Palmer Brown.
    - Correspondence Brown, 1963-1964 (Folder 425)
    - Correspondence Brown, 1964 (Folder 426)
    - Correspondence Brown, 1964 (Folder 427)
    - Correspondence Brown, 1964 (Folder 428)
    - Correspondence Brown, 1964 (Folder 429)
    - Correspondence Brown, 1965 (Folder 430)
    - Correspondence Brown, 1965 (Folder 431)
    - Correspondence Brown, 1965 (Folder 432)
    - Correspondence Brown, 1965-1966 (Folder 433)
    - Correspondence Brown, 1966 (Folder 434)
    - Correspondence Brown, 1966 (Folder 435)
    - Col-Her, 1963-1965 (Folder 436)
    - Photos, 1963-1965 (Folder 437)
    - Reports, 1963-1965 (Folder 438)
    - Misc., 1963-1965 (Folder 439)
    - Misc., 1963-1965 (Folder 440)
    - Misc., 1963-1965 (Folder 441)
  - Scholarship, 1951-1965 (Box 15, Folder 442-452)
    Correspondence in this subseries consists of correspondence related to how some winners chose to use their prize money from the Dupont Awards to give a small scholarship to journalism majors at various universities.
    - Bot-Dup, 1951-1966 (Folder 442)
    - Farrar, 1951-1966 (Folder 443)
    - Gai-Goo, 1951-1966 (Folder 444)
    - Haefele, 1961-1963 (Folder 445)
    - Haefele, 1964-1965 (Folder 446)
    - Hyl-Nel, 1951-1966 (Folder 447)
    - Scheuer, 1951-1966 (Folder 448)
    - Sha-Misc., 1951-1966 (Folder 449)
    - Instructions, 1951-1966 (Folder 450)
    - Photos and Publications, 1951-1966 (Folder 451)
    - Misc., 1951-1966 (Folder 452)
  - Speakers, 1951-1965 (Box 15, Folder 453-463)
    - Aba-Col, 1951-1966 (Folder 453)
    - Con-Fow, 1951-1966 (Folder 454)
    - Gei-Hok, 1951-1966 (Folder 455)
    - Hol-Hyd, 1951-1966 (Folder 456)
    - Jar-May, 1951-1966 (Folder 457)
    - McC-Paw, 1951-1966 (Folder 458)
    - Per-Shi, 1951-1966 (Folder 459)
    - Sim-Zel, 1951-1966 (Folder 460)
    - Photos and Statements, 1951-1966 (Folder 461)
    - Statements, 1951-1966 (Folder 462)
    - Misc., 1951-1966 (Folder 463)
  - State Radio and TV, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 464-465)
    - Alg-Lud, 1951-1966 (Folder 464)
    - Mar-Misc., 1951-1966 (Folder 465)
  - Symbol, 1959-1961 (Box 15, Folder 466-469)
    This subseries focuses on the process determining a logo for the Dupont Awards including correspondence, images, and sketches.
    - Col-Sha, 1951-1966 (Folder 466)
    - Photos, 1951-1966 (Folder 467)
    - Sketches, 1951-1966 (Folder 468)
    - Misc., 1951-1966 (Folder 469)
  - Award Winners, 1951-1965 (Box 16-17, Folder 470-528)
    Items in this sub-series consist of materials related to the presentation of the Dupont Awards to their respective winners. Because of the annual nature of the award, material is sorted by year and then by content.
    - Correspondence, 1951 (Folder 470)
    - Misc., 1951 (Folder 471)
    - Correspondence, 1952 (Folder 472)
    - Correspondence, 1952 (Folder 473)
    - Correspondence, 1952 (Folder 474)
    - Photos, 1952 (Folder 475)
    - Photos, 1952 (Folder 476)
    - Correspondence, 1953 (Folder 477)
    - Correspondence, 1953 (Folder 478)
    - Correspondence, 1953 (Folder 479)
    - Correspondence, 1953 (Folder 480)
    - Correspondence, 1953 (Folder 481)
    - Photos, 1953 (Folder 482)
    - Misc., 1953 (Folder 483)
    - Misc., 1953 (Folder 484)
    - Correspondence, 1954 (Folder 485)
    - Correspondence, 1954 (Folder 486)
    - Correspondence, 1954 (Folder 487)
    - Correspondence, 1954 (Folder 488)
    - Photos, 1954 (Folder 489)
    - Misc., 1954 (Folder 490)
    - Correspondence, 1955 (Folder 491)
    - Correspondence, 1955 (Folder 492)
    - Correspondence, 1955 (Folder 493)
    - Correspondence, 1956 (Folder 494)
    - Correspondence, 1957 (Folder 495)
    - Correspondence, 1957 (Folder 496)
    - Correspondence, 1957 (Folder 497)
    - Correspondence, 1957 (Folder 498)
    - Photos, 1957 (Folder 499)
    - Submissions, 1957 (Folder 500)
    - Misc., 1957 (Folder 501)
    - Correspondence, 1958 (Folder 502)
    - Correspondence, 1958 (Folder 503)
    - Correspondence, 1959 (Folder 504)
    - Correspondence, 1959 (Folder 505)
    - Misc., 1959 (Folder 506)
    - Correspondence, 1960 (Folder 507)
    - Correspondence, 1960 (Folder 508)
    - Correspondence, 1961 (Folder 509)
    - Correspondence, 1961 (Folder 510)
    - Misc., 1961 (Folder 511)
    - Correspondence, 1962 (Folder 512)
    - Correspondence, 1962 (Folder 513)
    - Correspondence, 1962 (Folder 514)
    - Misc., 1962 (Folder 515)
    - Acceptance Speeches and Biographical Data, 1963 (Folder 516)
    - Correspondence, 1963 (Folder 517)
    - Correspondence, 1963 (Folder 518)
    - Misc., 1963 (Folder 519)
    - Commentator Award Explanation, 1964 (Folder 520)
    - Correspondence, 1964 (Folder 521)
    - Misc., 1964 (Folder 522)
  - Miscellaneous, 1952-1966 (Box 17-18, Folder 523-530)
    The items in this sub-series consist of miscellaeous materials that did not necessarily fit with the other groupings. Along with the files listed are two scrap-books of remarks made at the Dupont Awards Dinner.
    - Misc., 1952-1959 (Folder 523)
    - Misc., 1963-1965 (Folder 524)
    - Misc., 1965-1966 (Folder 525)
    - Misc., 1966 (Folder 526)
    - Misc., 1951-1966 (Folder 527)
    - Misc., 1951-1966 (Folder 528)
    - Misc., 1951-1966 (Folder 529)
    - Misc., 1951-1966 (Folder 530)
  - Unprocessed Materials, 1950-1968 (Box 18a)
    Items in this subseries consist of materials that belong in the Journalism Department series but have not been processed into the collection yet.
- Autobiography: "Hacking It", 1982-1996; Riegel, O. W. (Oscar Wetherhold); 2.25 Linear Feet (Box 1-2, Folder 1-80)
  Items in this series consist of and are related to O.W. Riegel's unpublished memoir "Hacking It". The first section of the series contains the most refined drafts of the Autobiography. Then there is correspondence between individuals who assited Riegel in drafting and editing his work. There are also several unrefined drafts of material, and a couple of artifacts and notes related to the Memoir. Housed separately from the rest of the collection, is one box of Newspaper clippings sorted by topic around different subjects Riegel's memoir addresses.
  Riegel, O. W. (Oscar Wetherhold); Labro, Philippe
  - Autobiography, 1982-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1-12)
    This subseries contains the most up-to-date version of Riegel's unpublished autobiography.
    - Title Page, Table of contents, Prologue, 1982-1996 (Folder 1)
    - Chapter 1: University 1, 1982-1996 (Folder 2)
    - Chapter 1: University 2, 1982-1996 (Folder 3)
    - Chapter 2: Journalist, 1982-1996 (Folder 4)
    - Chapter 3: Young Man in Paris 1, 1982-1996 (Folder 5)
    - Chapter 3: Young Man in Paris 2, 1982-1996 (Folder 6)
    - Chapter 4: Dartmouth, 1982-1996 (Folder 7)
    - Chapter 5: "Reluctant Scholar", 1982-1996 (Folder 8)
    - Chapter 6: Europe 1932, 1982-1996 (Folder 9)
    - Chapter 8: The Waiting Years 1, 1982-1996 (Folder 10)
    - Chapter 8: The Waiting Years 2, 1982-1996 (Folder 11)
    - Chapter 9: In the Shadow of War, 1982-1996 (Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1982-1996 (Box 1, Folder 13-21)
    Correspondence in this subseries focuses on revisions of Riegel's memoirs and requests for information for Riegel to use in his writing.
    - Adrienne, 1982-1996 (Folder 13)
    - Ballou, 1982-1996 (Folder 14)
    - Ben-Buck, 1982-1996 (Folder 15)
    - Buckwalter-Gre, 1982-1996 (Folder 16)
    - Hai-Lab, 1982-1996 (Folder 17)
    - Lel-Ses, 1982-1996 (Folder 18)
    - Sha-Tur, 1982-1996 (Folder 19)
    - Misc. Bill-Trudy, 1982-1996 (Folder 20)
    - Misc., 1962-1996 (Folder 21)
  - Drafts, 1982-1996 (Box 1-2, Folder 22-63)
    Items in this subseries consist of various drafts on sections considered in the development of Riegel's Memoir. Topics range from his trip to the Virgin Islands, to his view of religion, and his year in Hungary after the conclusion of World War II.
    - Dynamo, 1982-1996 (Folder 22)
    - Lawrence University, 1982-1996 (Folder 23)
    - Summer 1922, 1982-1996 (Folder 24)
    - Summer 1923, 1982-1996 (Folder 25)
    - University 1 Typescript Original, 1982-1996 (Folder 26)
    - University 1 Second Draft, 1982-1996 (Folder 27)
    - Journalist Original, 1982-1996 (Folder 28)
    - Journalist: Dee's Copy, 1982-1996 (Folder 29)
    - Paris in the Twenties, 1982-1996 (Folder 30)
    - Lancaster, 1982-1996 (Folder 31)
    - Dartmouth Original, 1982-1996 (Folder 32)
    - Dartmouth: Kurt's Scanning of Section, 1982-1996 (Folder 33)
    - Reluctant Scholar Original, 1982-1996 (Folder 34)
    - 1932, 1982-1996 (Folder 35)
    - Summer 1932 Original, 1982-1996 (Folder 36)
    - Summer of 1933 Original, 1982-1996 (Folder 37)
    - Post-Starnberg, 1982-1996 (Folder 38)
    - The Waiting Years, 1982-1996 (Folder 39)
    - Shelter Original, 1982-1996 (Folder 40)
    - In the Shadow of War: Paris, 1982-1996 (Folder 41)
    - In the Shadow of War: Berlin Original, 1982-1996 (Folder 42)
    - In the Shadow of War: Berlin (1935), 1982-1996 (Folder 43)
    - Soviet Union Original, 1982-1996 (Folder 44)
    - Soviet Union Second Draft, 1982-1996 (Folder 45)
    - My War 1, 1982-1996 (Folder 46)
    - My War 3: The Propaganda Machine, 1982-1996 (Folder 47)
    - My War 4: The Winds of Word War, 1982-1996 (Folder 48)
    - My War 5: Wary Warrior, 1982-1996 (Folder 49)
    - Italia, 1982-1996 (Folder 50)
    - Italia Copy 2, 1982-1996 (Folder 51)
    - Hungary Remembered, 1982-1996 (Folder 52)
    - Hungary: Cultural Diplomacy, 1982-1996 (Folder 53)
    - Hungary Misc., 1982-1996 (Folder 54)
    - Introduction, 1982-1996 (Folder 55)
    - The Rich, 1982-1996 (Folder 56)
    - Me & Communism, 1982-1996 (Folder 57)
    - Virgin Islands: Part 1, 1982-1996 (Folder 58)
    - Virgin Islands Part 2, 1982-1996 (Folder 59)
    - Washing off the Patriotic Gore, 1982-1996 (Folder 60)
    - Religion, 1982-1996 (Folder 61)
    - Health Rules, Photo Files, & Snap Shots, 1982-1996 (Folder 62)
    - Misc., 1982-1996 (Folder 63)
  - Jane's Journal, 1982-1996 (Box 2, Folder 64-66)
    Items in this subseries relate to Jane Riegel's materials that were stored with Riegel's autobiography. Oscar Riegel had Jane's journal bound and printed as a gift. These items are the scans and illustrations of her journal that were necessary to make his gift possible.
    - Editing, 1966-1995 (Folder 64)
    - Illustrations, 1966-1995 (Folder 65)
    - Journal Scan, 1966-1995 (Folder 66)
  - Materials, 1982-1996 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Notes, 1982-1996 (Box 2, Folder 68-78)
    Items in this subseries consist of notes that Riegel took on various subjects related to his autobiography.
    - Autobiography: Dartmouth, 1982-1996 (Folder 68)
    - Autobiography: Revisions, 1982-1996 (Folder 69)
    - People, 1982-1996 (Folder 70)
    - People, 1982-1996 (Folder 71)
    - People, 1982-1996 (Folder 72)
    - People, 1982-1996 (Folder 73)
    - Personal, 1982-1996 (Folder 74)
    - The Problem, 1982-1996 (Folder 75)
    - Professional, 1982-1996 (Folder 76)
    - Censorship, 1982-1996 (Folder 77)
    - Misc., 1982-1996 (Folder 78)
  - Miscellaneous, 1982-1996 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Miscellaneous, 1982-1996 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Unprocessed Materials, 1982-1996 (Box 2a)
    Items in this subseries consist of aspects of Riegel's autiobiography that have not yet been processed into the collection.
- Journalism Department, 1932-1974; Riegel, O. W. (Oscar Wetherhold); 8.8 Linear Feet This series is primarily contained in large and medium size archival storage boxes. Additionally, there are two boxes of Newspaper Clippings related to the Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation and other aspects of the department that are stored separately from the rest of the series. (Box 1-12, Folder 1-524, Box 1-5, Box 11-13, Folder 508-526)
  Items in the Journalism Department series are based in the time period when Riegel was a member and later director of the department. sub-sections of this series include correspondence within the department, course materials, department seminars, accreditiation discussions,the Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation, the maintenance of the department's library, and publicity related to the department and its faculty. some items of note include some student work for classes, including a project by Phillipe Labro, a cartoonist awards program with signatures from various cartoonists including Charles Shultz, and various surveys related to higher education and journalism.
  Labro, Philippe; Riegel, O. W. (Oscar Wetherhold); Gaines, Francis Pendleton; Davis, J. Paxton; Lauck, Charles Harold; Booth, Augustus Lea; Shultz Charles
  - Accreditation, 1941-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1-11)
    As the department chair of Washington and Lee University's Journalism department, Riegel was responsible for its accreditation. This subseries consists of documents related to the accreditation status of Washington and Lee's Journalism department. The main agencies that Riegel worked with were the American Council on Education for Journalism, the American Association of Educators in Journalism, and the Association for Education in Journalism. Items are organized by year within each accreditation agency. Documents of note in this subseries include evaluation forms, correspondence about accreditation agency policy and goals, and annual accreditation reports.
    - American Association of Education in Journalism, 1941-1949 (Folder 1)
    - American Association of Education in Journalism, 1950-1964 (Folder 2)
    - American Council on Education for Journalism, 1947 (Folder 3)
    - American Council on Education for Journalism Feb.-Mar., 1947 (Folder 4)
    - American Council on Education for Journalism, 1947-1950 (Folder 5)
    - American Council on Education for Journalism, 1950-1951 (Folder 6)
    - American Council on Education for Journalism, 1951-1963 (Folder 7)
    - Association for Education in Journalism, 1949-1959 (Folder 8)
    - Association for Education in Journalism, 1960-1964 (Folder 9)
    - Misc., 1946-1953 (Folder 10)
    - Misc. (Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1932-1974 (Box 1-2, Folder 12-185)
    Items in this subseries consist of letters between Riegel and over 550 correspondents related to Washington and Lee's Journalism program. Letters range in theme from inquiries about the program, job openings for journalism graudates, the Associated Press, the British Library, the American Association of Schools with Departments in Journalism, and others.
    - Abb-Ack, 1932-1974 (Folder 12)
    - Adl-Allen C., 1932-1974 (Folder 13)
    - Allen E.-Alt, 1932-1974 (Folder 14)
    - American Association of Public Opinion Research, 1932-1974 (Folder 15)
    - Amercian Association of Schools with Departments of Journalism Bar-Cla, 1932-1974 (Folder 16)
    - Amercian Association of Schools with Departments of Journalism Fre-Mar, 1932-1974 (Folder 17)
    - Amercian Association of Schools with Departments of Journalism Mar-Mur, 1932-1974 (Folder 18)
    - Amercian Association of Schools with Departments of Journalism Mur-Ols, 1932-1974 (Folder 19)
    - Amercian Association of Schools with Departments of Journalism Ols-Wil, 1932-1974 (Folder 20)
    - Amercian Association of Schools with Departments of Journalism Misc., 1927-1962 (Folder 21)
    - Amercian Association of Schools with Departments of Journalism Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 22)
    - American Bar Association- American Newspaper Publishers Association, 1932-1974 (Folder 23)
    - American Press Society: AASDJ, 1932-1974 (Folder 24)
    - American Press Society: APS, 1936-1939 (Folder 25)
    - American Press Society: APS, 1939-1940 (Folder 26)
    - American Press Society Bos-Lou, 1932-1974 (Folder 27)